<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys</title>
    <description>The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys(ASPA) consists of members who are engaged in patent work in Singapore and registered with the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore (IPOS) as patent attorneys as well as members who are undergoing training to qualify as patent attorneys.
</description>
    <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.aspa.org.sg/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 22:01:10 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 22:01:10 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the New ASPA Website</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to introduce our newly redesigned website, which has a new look and is easier to navigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website was built by committee member Dr Chong-Yee Khoo, using &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://octopress.org&quot;&gt;Octopress&lt;/a&gt;. It uses the &lt;a href=&quot;http://getbootstrap.com&quot;&gt;Bootstrap&lt;/a&gt; framework.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/08/03/new-aspa-website</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/08/03/new-aspa-website</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5th Global Forum on Intellectual Property 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA is pleased to be a supporting organisation of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipos.gov.sg/ipweek2015/&quot;&gt;5th Global Forum on Intellectual Property 2015&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipos.gov.sg/ipweek2015/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/gfip-2015.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;GFIP&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GFIP brings together internationally renowned IP legal practitioners, policy makers, members of the judiciary, academics and business leaders to share insights and strategies through a series of highly focused discussions on the latest trends and issues in the highly-evolving global IP and economic landscapes. The sterling ensemble of speakers and thought-provoking plenaries and workshops at each conference has made GFIP a must-attend event for IP leaders in the region, giving participants an opportunity to meet the Who’s Who in IP from the region and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Minister for Law will be the Guest of Honour and deliver the opening address. Other IP luminaries and policy-makers who will be speaking at GFIP 2015 include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dr. Francis Gurry, Director-General, WIPO&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Justice Colin Birss from the UK&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Simon Thorley, QC and International Judge from the Singapore International Commercialisation Court&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Judicial Commissioner George Wei&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key highlights of GFIP 2015 are-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ASEAN Economic Integration: Interoperability and Synergies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Special Judges’ Plenary Session with eminent Judges from the UK, US, China, India and Singapore&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insights into recent high-profile IP litigation cases from around the world&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discussions on IP &amp;amp; New/Disruptive Technologies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strategies for IP value creation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GFIP 2015 is also the anchor event of IP Week @ SG 2015, organized by IPOS. IP Week @ SG 2015 will be a celebration of Singapore’s achievements and milestones in IP and will showcase IP that has impacted our lives. With public talks, exhibitions and IP meeting points, this event will provide even more networking opportunities to participants and sponsors of GFIP 2015. Please refer to the following URL for more information on GFIP 2015 and IP Week @ SG 2015&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 21:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/07/07/global-forum-on-intellectual-property</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/07/07/global-forum-on-intellectual-property</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thirteenth Annual General Meeting</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA held its 13th Annual General Meeting today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/05/28/thirteenth-annual-general-meeting</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/05/28/thirteenth-annual-general-meeting</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA Christmas Lunch</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2014/12/12/aspa-christmas-lunch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2014/12/12/aspa-christmas-lunch</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seminar With EPO Biotech Examiners</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Biotech patenting in Europe - a seminar by experts from the European Patent Office
&lt;!--more--&gt;
Summary:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The European Patent Office grants patents for the 38 contracting states of the European Patent Convention covering a market of 600 million people. It will soon be possible to reduce the costs of a European patent after grant by requesting “unitary effect” across 25 EU member states. Any litigation involving this supranational patent will be at a Unified Patent Court using a centralised procedure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The EPO is the world’s most popular searching authority under the PCT procedure and places great importance on meeting PCT users’ expectations with regard to quality and timeliness. Thanks to fruitful collaboration with other patent offices, EPO examiners now have one-click access to the work done by their colleagues at the USPTO, SIPO, KIPO and JPO (with automatic translations) - a public version called “the Global Dossier” already covers EPO and SIPO patent filings, and is to grow over the coming years. It is now possible for an EPO examiner to classify and retrieve technical information in patent applications (even when they are in Japanese!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using a real case, we will demonstrate the tools developed in-house for searching of 1) DNA/protein sequences, 2) fulltext of patent and scientific literature 3) non-Boolean searching.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will also explain the principles of patenting second medical uses and personalised medicine. These claim formats are specific to biotech in Europe and have no equivalents in the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The presentations will be given by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dr Athanassios-Andreas Stamatopoulos
Principal director of Biotechnology, Pharmacy and organic chemistry, leading over 200 examiners in Biotechnology and around 300 examiners in Pure &amp;amp; Applied Organic Chemistry.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dr Ulrich Thiele
Director of a unit in the Biotechnology cluster leading a group of 30 examiners in the field of protein based and nucleic acid based analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dr Matthias Ulbrecht
Senior examiner in nucleic acid diagnostics and immunology. Matthias has exert knowledge on patenting of patents relating to personalized medicine and has established the principles for harmonized examination of such cases.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dr  Fredrik Åslund
Senior examiner in nucleic acid diagnostics and genetic engineering. Fredrik has worked with Matthias on writing up guidelines for the handling of SNP related cases. Fredrik is also the Biotech co-ordinator for presentations of EPO at trade fairs such as Biopharma Asia 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2014/10/01/seminar-with-epo-biotech-examiners</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2014/10/01/seminar-with-epo-biotech-examiners</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twelfth Annual General Meeting</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA held its 12th Annual General Meeting today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2014/05/29/twelfth-annual-general-meeting</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2014/05/29/twelfth-annual-general-meeting</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA Christmas Lunch</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2013/12/06/aspa-christmas-lunch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2013/12/06/aspa-christmas-lunch</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eleventh Annual General Meeting</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA held its 11th Annual General Meeting today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 07:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2013/06/25/eleventh-annual-general-meeting</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2013/06/25/eleventh-annual-general-meeting</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA Christmas and End of Year Lunch</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2012/12/14/aspa-christmas-and-end-of-year-lunch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2012/12/14/aspa-christmas-and-end-of-year-lunch</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tenth Annual General Meeting</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA held its 10th Annual General Meeting today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2012/06/14/tenth-annual-general-meeting</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2012/06/14/tenth-annual-general-meeting</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
