<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA)</title>
    <description>The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA) is the only organisation dedicated solely to the representation of the patent profession in Singapore. Our members are patent attorneys and patent agents registered with IPOS as well as those undergoing training to qualify as patent attorneys.
</description>
    <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.aspa.org.sg/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:32:05 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:32:05 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>IP Week 2025</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA) is pleased to be a supporting organisation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipweek2025.sg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;IP Week @ SG 2025&lt;a&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Supporting Organization, ASPA has committed to promoting the event and encouraging our members to participate. We believe that IP Week @ SG 2025 will provide valuable insights and opportunities for professional development, and we encourage you to register for the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please refer to the following for the dates and venue of the event and the registration details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore (IPOS) at IP Week @ SG 2025, the premier Intellectual Property event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Date: 26 to 27 August 2025&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Location: Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre (MBS), Singapore&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Into its fourteenth edition, IP Week @ SG 2025 is the world’s premier Intellectual Property (IP) event which brings together IP thought leaders, legal experts, and innovative enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Register &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipweek2025.sg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;a&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:06:57 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2025/06/05/ip-week-2025/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2025/06/05/ip-week-2025/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA CNCPI IPTA Joint Webinar 2025</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;out-with-the-old-in-with-the-new--2025-ip-trends-in-singapore-australia-and-france&quot;&gt;Out with the Old, in with the New – 2025 IP trends in Singapore, Australia and France&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA), CNCPI - Compagnie Nationale des Conseils en Propriété Industrielle (France) and the Institute of Patent and Trade Mark Attorneys of Australia (IPTA) are pleased to present a joint webinar on 9 April 2025.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speakers from the three professional organisations will talk on patent and trade mark prosecution and litigation in their respective jurisdictions (Singapore, France and Australia).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;programme&quot;&gt;Programme&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;introductions&quot;&gt;Introductions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ASPA - Singapore: Low Pei Lin&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IPTA - Australia: John Landells (incoming President)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CNCPI - France: Emmanuel Potdevin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;presentations-and-speaker-profiles&quot;&gt;Presentations and Speaker Profiles&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fast Track or Slow Lane? Strategies for Accelerating and Delaying Patent Prosecution in Singapore&lt;/em&gt; - Chong-Yee Khoo (ASPA)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lessons in Honesty - an Update on Recent Australian Court Decisions on Honesty of Adoption and Use of Trademarks and the Importance of Clearance Searching&lt;/em&gt; - Lauren Eade (IPTA)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Redesigning the Future: The EU’s New Legislative Package&lt;/em&gt; - Frédéric Glaize (CNCPI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;speaker-profiles&quot;&gt;Speaker Profiles&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dr-chong-yee-khoo-cantab-ip-pte-ltd&quot;&gt;Dr Chong-Yee Khoo (Cantab IP Pte Ltd)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Chong-Yee Khoo is a life sciences patent attorney with over 29 years of experience in private practice and industry. He is a Chartered Patent Attorney (UK) and Fellow of CIPA, European Patent Attorney, Registered Singapore Patent Agent, European Patent Litigator and ISTMA Registered Trade Mark Agent. His practice involves drafting, prosecuting and defending patents worldwide in a broad range of biotech, pharma, life sciences and related subject matter. Dr Khoo has postgraduate research experience with a Ph.D. from Cambridge University, where he also obtained a double first class honours degree in Natural Sciences. He is an author on two &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt; papers and one in &lt;em&gt;Current Biology&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chong-Yee is a qualified orchid judge accredited to the British Orchid Council. In his spare time, he is a keen road cyclist, photographer and computer programmer. He enjoys cricket as a spectator and listening to the music of Stephen Sondheim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lauren-eade-davies-collison-cave&quot;&gt;Lauren Eade (Davies Collison Cave)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lauren has more than 15 years’ experience in trademark practice and intellectual property commercialisation. Lauren also undertook a sabbatical in the UK completing a Masters of Law studies at the Centre for Commercial Law Studies of the Queen Mary &amp;amp; Westfield College of the University of London in the field of international and comparative intellectual property law, focusing on European, American and Australian trademark law. She has written extensively in this and related areas of law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;frédéric-glaize-plasseraud-ip&quot;&gt;Frédéric Glaize (Plasseraud IP)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frédéric Glaize is the chair of the Design and Copyright committee at CNCPI and co-chair of the Design committee of the French Group of AIPPI. Frédéric leads the Design department at Plasseraud IP, where he has been a partner since 2020. He is a former member of the jury for the Professional Qualification Examination of the French trademark and design attorneys. He is also a regular contributor to legal publications for which he writes on design law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;webinar-details&quot;&gt;Webinar Details&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9 April 2025 at&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;France: 8:30 am&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Singapore: 2:30 pm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Melbourne, Sydney, Canberra, Brisbane: 4:30 pm (AEST)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adelaide: 4:00 pm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perth: 2:30 pm (AWST)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New Zealand: 6:30 pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2025/03/28/ipta-aspa-cncpi-joint-webinar-2025/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2025/03/28/ipta-aspa-cncpi-joint-webinar-2025/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA End of Year Lunch 2024</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA’s annual end-of-year festive lunch will be held this year on Friday, 6 December 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Date: 1 December 2024&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Time: 12 noon to 2 pm&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Venue: OSO Ristorante, 100 Peck Seah Street, #27th Floor, Oasia Hotel Downtown, Singapore 079333 (Tanjong Pagar MRT Station)
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/aspa-year-end-lunch-6-december-2024-tickets-1028712164777?aff=oddtdtcreator&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;button type=&quot;button&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary float-end&quot;&gt;Sign Up for Event&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m14!1m8!1m3!1d15955.3168017819!2d103.8442824!3d1.275835!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x31da196d5a66549b%3A0xf798e806cca1cb5d!2sOSO%20Ristorante!5e0!3m2!1sen!2ssg!4v1696330124161!5m2!1sen!2ssg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; style=&quot;border:0;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;no-referrer-when-downgrade&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An email invite has been to all members. If you wish to attend, please RSVP as soon as possible, as places are limited.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 22:09:29 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2024/11/16/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2024/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2024/11/16/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2024/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA CIPSA Joint Webinar 2024</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA) and the Capital Intellectual Services Association (CIPSA) are pleased to present a joint webinar on 22 July 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speakers from the professional organisations will talk on patent prosecution and patent litigation in their respective jurisdictions (Singapore and China).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;webinar-details&quot;&gt;Webinar Details&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;22 July 2024 from 2 pm to 3:15 pm Singapore Time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;programme&quot;&gt;Programme&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;13:45 hrs to 14:00 hrs: Sign In&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;14:00 hrs: Opening Remarks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;14:10 Start&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;14:10 hrs to 14:30 hrs: Latest Developments in the Chinese Patent System and Strategies for Patent Procurement and Enforcement (Peter Zhang, CIPSA)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;14:30 hrs to 14:35 hrs: Question and Answer Session&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;14:35 hrs to 14:55 hrs: Features of Patent Litigation in Singapore; The New Simplified Track for IP - Cases in the Singapore Courts (Oh Pin-Ping, ASPA)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;14:55 hrs to 15:00 hrs: Question and Answer Session&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;15:00 hrs to 15:20 hrs: Patent Enablement and Sufficiency in Singapore: the Court of Appeal Decision in Ila Technologies v Element Six (Dr. Khoo Chong-Yee, ASPA)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;15:20 hrs to 15:25 hrs: Question and Answer Session&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;15:25 hrs: End&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;speaker-profiles&quot;&gt;Speaker Profiles&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;oh-pin-ping&quot;&gt;Oh Pin-Ping&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pin-Ping is an IP partner in the international law firm, Bird &amp;amp; Bird. She is an attorney at law as well as a Registered Singapore Patent Attorney. Pin-Ping’s practice straddles both contentious and non-contentious IP, including acting for clients in patent infringement lawsuits before the Singapore courts, and advising clients on patent freedom to operate, infringement and validity
issues. She also co-heads the patent prosecution practice in Bird &amp;amp; Bird’s Singapore office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dr-chong-yee-khoo&quot;&gt;Dr Chong-Yee Khoo&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Chong-Yee Khoo is a life sciences patent attorney with over 28 years experience in private practice and industry. He is a Chartered Patent Attorney and Fellow of CIPA, a European Patent Attorney and a Registered Singapore Patent Agent. He also holds an Intellectual Property Litigation Certificate and is a Unified Patent Court (UPC) Representative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chong-Yee has extensive experience in drafting, prosecuting and defending patents worldwide in a broad range of biotech, pharma, life sciences and related subject matter. His clients include academia, SMEs and MNCs in Asia, Europe, and the US. He has experience in industry, having been seconded as an in-house patent attorney to a large Danish diagnostics company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before founding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cantab-ip.com/&quot;&gt;Cantab IP&lt;/a&gt;, he was a partner at one of the leading firms of patent and trade mark attorneys in the United Kingdom. Dr Khoo has postgraduate research experience with a Ph.D. from Cambridge University, where he also
obtained a double first class honours degree in Natural Sciences. He is an author on two &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt; papers and one in &lt;em&gt;Current Biology&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chong-Yee is a qualified orchid judge accredited to the British Orchid Council. In his spare time, he is a keen road cyclist, photographer, and computer programmer. He enjoys cricket as a spectator and listening to the music of Stephen Sondheim.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 12:09:08 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2024/07/16/aspa-cipsa-joint-webinar-2024/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2024/07/16/aspa-cipsa-joint-webinar-2024/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IP Week 2024</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA) is pleased to be a supporting organisation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipweek2024.sg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;IP Week @ SG 2024&lt;a&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Supporting Organization, ASPA has committed to promoting the event and encouraging our members to participate. We believe that IP Week @ SG 2024 will provide valuable insights and opportunities for professional development, and we encourage you to register for the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please refer to the following for the dates and venue of the event and the registration details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore (IPOS) at IP Week @ SG 2024, the premier Intellectual Property event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Date: 27 to 28 August 2024&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Location: Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre (MBS), Singapore&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Into its thirteenth edition, IP Week @ SG 2024 is the world’s premier Intellectual Property (IP) event which brings together IP thought leaders, legal experts, and innovative enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Register &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipweek2024.sg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;a&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:13:08 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2024/07/10/ip-week-2024/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2024/07/10/ip-week-2024/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA CNCPI IPTA Joint Webinar 2024</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA), CNCPI - Compagnie Nationale des Conseils en Propriété Industrielle and the Institute of Patent and Trade Mark Attorneys of Australia (IPTA) are pleased to present a joint webinar on 8 April 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speakers from the three professional organisations will talk on patent prosecution and patent litigation in their respective jurisdictions (Singapore, France and Australia).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;webinar-details&quot;&gt;Webinar Details&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8 April 2024 at&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;France: 9:30 am to 11:30 am&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Singapore: 3:30 pm to 5:30 pm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Melbourne, Sydney, Canberra, Brisbane: 5:30 pm to 7:30 pm (AEST)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adelaide: 5:00 pm to 7:00 pm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perth: 3:30 pm to 5:30 pm (AWST)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New Zealand: 7:30 pm to 9:30 pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;programme&quot;&gt;Programme&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;introductions&quot;&gt;Introductions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chairwomen of ASPA, CNCPI and IPTA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ASPA - Singapore: Low Pei Lin&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CNCPI - France: Guylène Kiesel le Cosquer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IPTA - Australia: Jennifer McEwan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;presentations&quot;&gt;Presentations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Patent Litigation in Singapore: Oh Pin Ping (ASPA)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Patent Prosecution in Singapore: Chong-Yee Khoo (ASPA)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CNCPI: Jérémie Palacci&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CNCPI: Henri Bourgeois&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IPTA: Philip Gehrig&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IPTA: Will Hird&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;speaker-profiles&quot;&gt;Speaker Profiles&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;oh-pin-ping&quot;&gt;Oh Pin-Ping&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pin-Ping is an IP partner in the international law firm, Bird &amp;amp; Bird. She is an attorney at law as well as a Registered Singapore Patent Attorney. Pin-Ping’s practice straddles both contentious and non-contentious IP, including acting for clients in patent infringement lawsuits before the Singapore courts, and advising clients on patent freedom to operate, infringement and validity
issues. She also co-heads the patent prosecution practice in Bird &amp;amp; Bird’s Singapore office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dr-chong-yee-khoo&quot;&gt;Dr Chong-Yee Khoo&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Chong-Yee Khoo is a life sciences patent attorney with over 28 years experience in private practice and industry. He is a Chartered Patent Attorney and Fellow of CIPA, a European Patent Attorney and a Registered Singapore Patent Agent. He also holds an Intellectual Property Litigation Certificate and is a Unified Patent Court (UPC) Representative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chong-Yee has extensive experience in drafting, prosecuting and defending patents worldwide in a broad range of biotech, pharma, life sciences and related subject matter. His clients include academia, SMEs and MNCs in Asia, Europe, and the US. He has experience in industry, having been seconded as an in-house patent attorney to a large Danish diagnostics company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before founding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cantab-ip.com/&quot;&gt;Cantab IP&lt;/a&gt;, he was a partner at one of the leading firms of patent and trade mark attorneys in the United Kingdom. Dr Khoo has postgraduate research experience with a Ph.D. from Cambridge University, where he also
obtained a double first class honours degree in Natural Sciences. He is an author on two &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt; papers and one in &lt;em&gt;Current Biology&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chong-Yee is a qualified orchid judge accredited to the British Orchid Council. In his spare time, he is a keen road cyclist, photographer, and computer programmer. He enjoys cricket as a spectator and listening to the music of Stephen Sondheim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;philip-gehrig&quot;&gt;Philip Gehrig&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Philip GEHRIG is a Councillor of IPTA and is currently Co-Convenor of the Patents &amp;amp; Plant Breeders Rights Committee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Philip holds a Bachelor of Engineering Degree with Honours from the University of Melbourne. He specializes in the fields of patents and designs
and his experience spans a range of engineering technologies, including aeronautical and aerospace construction, medical devices, mining and agricultural equipment, manufacturing processes, gaming systems, software architecture, clean energy, and consumer products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Philip worked for several years in Germany where he qualified as a European patent attorney and a German patent attorney (Patentanwalt). He has coordinated IPTA’s submissions to IP Australia on the patentability of computer-implemented inventions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Philip is a Principal of the firm Wrays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;william-hird&quot;&gt;William Hird&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;William HIRD is a Councillor of IPTA and is currently Co-Convenor of the Patents &amp;amp; Plant Breeders Rights Committee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;William joined the patent attorney profession in 1998 and has since worked in private practice. He joined IPTA council in April 2017 where he took on the role of Convenor of the International Patents Committee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He coordinated IPTA’s submissions on grace periods, conflicting applications, and prior user rights at the Industry Symposium held in Munich in June 2017 including members of Group B+ and industry stakeholders. He also coordinated IPTA’s submission to the consultation paper on The Hague Conference Draft Convention on the Recognition and Enforcement of Foreign Judgments in April 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;William is a Principal of the firm Davies Collison Cave.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 19:12:19 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2024/03/21/ipta-aspa-cncpi-joint-webinar-2024/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2024/03/21/ipta-aspa-cncpi-joint-webinar-2024/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA End of Year Lunch 2023</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA’s annual end-of-year festive lunch will be held this year on Friday, 2 December 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Date: 1 December 2023&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Time: 12 noon to 2:30 pm&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Venue: OSO Ristorante, 100 Peck Seah Street, #27th Floor, Oasia Hotel Downtown, Singapore 079333 (Tanjong Pagar MRT Station)
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/aspa-year-end-lunch-1-december-2023-tickets-720992988437&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;button type=&quot;button&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary float-end&quot;&gt;Sign Up for Event&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m14!1m8!1m3!1d15955.3168017819!2d103.8442824!3d1.275835!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x31da196d5a66549b%3A0xf798e806cca1cb5d!2sOSO%20Ristorante!5e0!3m2!1sen!2ssg!4v1696330124161!5m2!1sen!2ssg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; style=&quot;border:0;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;no-referrer-when-downgrade&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An email invite has been to all members. If you wish to attend, please RSVP as soon as possible, as places are limited.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:18:45 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2023/10/03/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2023/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2023/10/03/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2023/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA Annual General Meeting 2023</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Annual General Meeting of the Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys will be held on 27 June 2023 at 5 pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Date: 27 June 2023&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Time: 6 pm to 9 pm (including dinner)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Venue: Mastercard Asia Pacific HQ, 15th Floor, 3 Fraser Street, Duo Tower, Singapore 189352&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/aspa-annual-general-meeting-agm-tickets-616963523507&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;button type=&quot;button&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary float-end&quot;&gt;RSVP&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Formal notice of the AGM will be sent to members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would help if you could please complete the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/aspa-annual-general-meeting-agm-tickets-616963523507&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RSVP for the Annual General Meeting&lt;/a&gt; so that we have some idea of how many will turn up for the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 17:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2023/04/13/aspa-annual-general-meeting-2023/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2023/04/13/aspa-annual-general-meeting-2023/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KPAA ASPA Joint Webinar 2023</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA) and the Korean Patent Attorneys Association (KPAA) held a joint webinar on 23 March 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program featured presentations from Korean and Singapore patent attorneys on patent prosecution and litigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;programme&quot;&gt;Programme&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Opening by Presidents of KPAA and ASPA&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“Preliminary Examination Program” by Mr. Lee Jaeyun (KPAA)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“Patent Prosecution in Singapore” by Dr Khoo Chong Yee (ASPA)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“Patent Prosecution In Korea” by Ms. Choi Hyun Jung (KPAA)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“Patent Enforcement in Singapore – New Rules of Court 2021 &amp;amp; New Simplified Process for IP Claims” by Ms Oh Pin Ping (ASPA)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Q&amp;amp;A and Social (20 mins)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 20:04:15 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2023/03/23/kpaa-aspa-joint-seminar-2023/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2023/03/23/kpaa-aspa-joint-seminar-2023/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA End of Year Lunch 2022</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA’s annual end-of-year festive lunch will be held this year on Friday, 2 December 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Date: 2 December 2022&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Time: 12 noon to 2:30 pm&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Venue: QIN Restaurant &amp;amp; Bar, 10 Cross Street, Level 5, Singapore 048417 (opposite Telok Ayer MRT Station)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.sg/e/aspa-year-end-gathering-2-dec-2022-tickets-411072277247&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;button type=&quot;button&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary float-end&quot;&gt;Sign Up for Event&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d3988.818569751687!2d103.84603705142115!3d1.282673062137638!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x31da19397f610f7f%3A0x68411534c45d52fc!2sQIN%20Restaurant%20%26%20Bar!5e0!3m2!1sen!2ssg!4v1661940974727!5m2!1sen!2ssg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; style=&quot;border:0;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;no-referrer-when-downgrade&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An email invite will sent shortly to all members. If you wish to attend, please RSVP as soon as possible, as places are limited.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:11:39 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2022/08/31/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2022/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2022/08/31/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2022/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
