<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA)</title>
    <description>The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA) is the only organisation dedicated solely to the representation of the patent profession in Singapore. Our members are patent attorneys and patent agents registered with IPOS as well as those undergoing training to qualify as patent attorneys.
</description>
    <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.aspa.org.sg/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 14:32:35 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 14:32:35 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA Intellectual Property Seminar with CIPA</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce that we will be holding a half-day seminar on IP topics in early October, presented by a delegation from the UK Chartered Institute of Patent Attorneys (CIPA).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The seminar will deal with topics of current interest in intellectual property, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;the impact of Brexit on European intellectual property&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;developments in European litigation procedure&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;the role of the Chartered Institute&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;conflicts of interest&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3D trade marks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;developments in design law&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The seminar will provide excellent networking opportunities over tea-breaks and lunch. It is open to all ordinary and associate members of ASPA as well as non-members. Advocates and solicitors who have an interest in IP law are welcome to attend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Details of the seminar are as follow:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Date: 5 October 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 12 noon to 5 pm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Venue: Pacific 1 Ballroom, Pan Pacific Hotel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cost: $30 members, $120 non-members (including lunch and tea breaks)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CPD: SILE CPD Points Pending&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For full details of the event, please see the &lt;a href=&quot;/events/cipa-seminar-2016&quot;&gt;ASPA CIPA IP Seminar page&lt;/a&gt;. Please register for the event at the &lt;a href=&quot;/events/cipa-seminar-2016/register&quot;&gt;registration page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;btn btn-default&quot; href=&quot;/events/cipa-seminar-2016/register&quot; role=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Register for Event &amp;raquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 14:43:54 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/09/01/intellectual-property-seminar-with-cipa/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/09/01/intellectual-property-seminar-with-cipa/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Japan Patent Attorneys Association Visit and Seminar</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA was honoured to receive a delegation from the Japan Patent Attorneys Association (APAA) during a visit to Singapore in January 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/news/2016/04/20/japan-patent-attorneys-association-visit-and-seminar/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/jpaa-visit-seminar-2016.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;JPAA Visit and Seminar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The visit to ASPA started with a meeting between the JPAA delegation and the ASPA Executive Committee. We discussed topics of interest to both sides and ASPA Exco members provided updates on Singapore IP law and practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the meeting, the JPAA kindly gave a presentation on “&lt;a href=&quot;/files/outline-of-patent-infringement-litigation-in-japan.pdf&quot;&gt;Patent Infringement Litigation in Japan&lt;/a&gt;” to ASPA members. The presentation was delivered by Mr Naoki Okumura of the JPAA International Activities Center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ASPA appreciates the opportunity to exchange views with the JPAA and we believe that such exchanges are mutually beneficial. ASPA members also appreciated the insights provided during the presentation on patent infringement in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look forward to further cooperation with JPAA in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 11:01:08 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/04/20/japan-patent-attorneys-association-visit-and-seminar/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/04/20/japan-patent-attorneys-association-visit-and-seminar/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA Comments on Draft Examination Guidelines for Patent Applications at IPOS</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA was invited by the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore to review and make comments on a proposed draft revision of the Examination Guidelines for Patent Applications at IPOS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ipos.gov.sg/Portals/0/1%20%20Examination%20Guidelines%20for%20Patent%20Applications%20at%20IPOS_ver%20Apr%202015.pdf&quot;&gt;current version of the examination guidelines&lt;/a&gt; was published by IPOS in April 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed revisions are to Chapter 8 of the Guidelines and seek to clarify IPOS’s position on  examination practices regarding patentable subject matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to this invitation, ASPA submitted its &lt;a href=&quot;/files/aspa-comments-on-patent-examination-guidelines-january-2016.pdf&quot;&gt;comments on the proposed revisions to the examination guidelines&lt;/a&gt; in January 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The submissions refer to an earlier &lt;a href=&quot;/files/email-from-aspa-to-ipos-8-may-2015.txt&quot;&gt;email dated 8 May 2015 from ASPA to IPOS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 15:42:21 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/02/02/aspa-comments-on-draft-examination-guidelines-for-patent-applications-at-ipos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/02/02/aspa-comments-on-draft-examination-guidelines-for-patent-applications-at-ipos/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA Engages With UK Patent Attorneys</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Asian Patent Attorneys Association (APAA) 17th General Assembly 64th and 65th Council Meetings were held recently in Okinawa, Japan. Several members of ASPA’s Executive Committee attended this meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the meeting, we took the opportunity to make contact with members of the International Liaison Committee of the UK Chartered Institute of Patent Attorneys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CIPA’s International Liaison Committee is responsible for co-operation with sister institutes in countries outside Europe, including the organisation of meetings between delegates of CIPA with representatives of overseas bodies both in the UK and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to make contact with CIPA and are actively exploring the possibility of joint events between CIPA and ASPA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://news.cipa.org.uk/20CI-3XB55-58E6171L5B/cr.aspx&quot;&gt;CIPA’s Christmas Newsletter 2015&lt;/a&gt; features a writeup on the meeting with ASPA:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Members of CIPA’s International Liaison Committee have also met with senior members of patent and trade mark attorney institutes from Australia, New Zealand, Taiwan, Singapore and Indonesia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A delegation from CIPA’s International Liaison Committee, led by Chairman Richard Mair, visited Japan as observers at the Asian Patent Attorneys Association’s General Assembly. While at the event, in Okinawa, Richard and the group met attorneys from sister institutes from around the Pacific Rim to reinforce the benefits of working with the UK profession…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“While at APAA we took the opportunity to meet with sister institutes that we would otherwise find difficulty in visiting due to budgets and distances involved,” said Richard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The meetings with our Australian and Taiwanese colleagues have become annual fixtures. This year we also held preliminary meetings with institutes in Singapore, New Zealand and Indonesia. So I was pleased to continue strengthening existing relations and to be able to develop new ones.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 11:23:55 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/01/15/aspa-engages-with-uk-patent-attorneys/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/01/15/aspa-engages-with-uk-patent-attorneys/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Visit of Delegation From Japan Patent Attorneys Association</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce that a delegation from the Japan Patent Attorneys Association (JPAA) will be visiting us on 20 January 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the visit, JPAA has kindly offered to give a talk “Outline of Patent Infringement Litigation in Japan” to ASPA members. All members are invited to attend this talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The talk will be held from 5 pm on 6.30 pm on 20 January 2016 at the Level 37 Conference Room of Spruson &amp;amp; Ferguson (Asia), at 152 Beach Road, Gateway East, Singapore 189721.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in attending the event, please get in touch with the Secretary by 31 December 2015 to register. We look forward to seeing you at the event.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 13:11:40 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/12/22/visit-of-delegation-from-japan-patent-attorneys-association/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/12/22/visit-of-delegation-from-japan-patent-attorneys-association/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA Response to Public Consultation on Designs</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Law and the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore held a &lt;a href=&quot;/files/public-consultation-paper-proposed-changes-to-singapore-registered-designs-regime.pdf&quot;&gt;public consultation&lt;/a&gt; on proposed changes to the registered designs system in Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After seeking members’ views, we filed a &lt;a href=&quot;/files/aspa-response-to-public-consultation-on-designs.pdf&quot;&gt;response to the consultation&lt;/a&gt; in mid-December 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 12:47:50 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/12/22/aspa-response-to-public-consultation-on-designs/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/12/22/aspa-response-to-public-consultation-on-designs/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASPA End of Year Lunch</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA’s annual end-of-year lunch will be held this year on Friday, 4 December 2015. &lt;del&gt;More details will be available soon, but please keep the date free.&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of the cost of the meal for members will be subsidised by ASPA, with a nominal fee payable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Update 1 November 2015&lt;/em&gt;: the lunch will be held from 12:30 pm at Zafferano. An invitation has been sent to members by email; please get in touch with the Secretary if you haven’t received yours.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 16:29:55 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/09/18/year-end-lunch/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/09/18/year-end-lunch/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JPAA Annual Patent Attorney’s Day and President’s Meeting</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA was invited to take part in the Annual Patent Attorney’s Day and President’s Meeting organised by the Japanese Patent Attorneys Association (JPAA). Mr Desmond Tan, Secretary of ASPA, attended the event on behalf of ASPA and provided this trip report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Annual Patent Attorney’s Day and President’s Meeting was held on 1 July 2015 at Hotel Okura, Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invited Attendees of JPAA included:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mr Kenji Yoshida (Immediate Past President, Asian Patent Attorneys Association)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mr Jiancheng Jiang (Vice President, All-China Patent Attorneys Association)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mr Lawrence T Welch (Member of IP Practice In Japan Committee, American Intellectual Property Law Association)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mr Shogo Ohnishi (President, Federation International des Counseils en Propriete Intellectuelle (FICPI) Japan)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mr Jeong-Ho Shin (Director of International Affairs, Korean Patent Attorneys Association)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mr Desmond Tan (Secretary, Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;presidents-meeting-from-3pm--430pm&quot;&gt;President’s Meeting (from 3pm – 4.30pm)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Topics discussed included the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Brief discussion on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fiveipoffices.org/activities/globaldossier.html&quot;&gt;Global Dossier (GD)&lt;/a&gt; and its objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr Yoshida mentioned that the APAA is supportive of the GD and believes that both applicants and practitioners will benefit from the GD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr Welch shared insights from engaging with the IP5 patent offices and WIPO on both the GD and ePCT when representing AIPLA. He mentioned that the IP5 offices are committed to the workability of the GD and WIPO is maintaining a watch on the progress of the GD as their own ePCT system is gradually implemented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr Tan asked if utility models/innovation patents would be already a part of/soon-to-be a part of the GD and the answer was negative. He suggested that the situation should be reversed since utility models/innovation patents are able to serve as priority documents for regular patents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr Jiang shared insights that the number of utility model applications in China is substantial, and agrees with Mr Tan’s suggestion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr Tan expressed appreciation for giving ASPA the opportunity to indirectly participate in the GD initiative, as the only groups currently involved are the Japan Intellectual Property Association, Business Europe, the Korean Intellectual Property Association, the Patent Protection Association Of China, the American Intellectual Property Law Association, and the Intellectual Property Owners Association. He mentioned that allowing ASPA to be involved via the JPAA is appreciated by ASPA given that Singapore’s small domestic market size limits the country’s impact on a global basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr Welch shared a view that the GD would be beneficial for practitioners as it is anticipated that filing numbers will increase after the introduction of the GD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr Tan provided a comment that when ASPA did an assessment in relation to the impact of ePCT on the practitioners in Singapore, the assessment was that the practitioners would benefit. Given that the principles of the GD mirror those of ePCT, he thus believes that the implementation of the GD would be beneficial for the practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/jpaa-patent-attorneys-day-presidents-meeting-2015-meeting.jpg&quot; title=&quot;jpaa-patent-attorneys-day-presidents-meeting-2015-meeting&quot; alt=&quot;jpaa-patent-attorneys-day-presidents-meeting-2015-meeting&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;informal-meeting-with-jpaa-committee-members-430pm--6pm&quot;&gt;Informal Meeting With JPAA Committee Members (4.30pm – 6pm)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the invited attendees were hosted by a number of JPAA committee members for informal discussions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A common topic for discussion centred on the APAA conference which is being held in Okinawa in November. Issues discussed ranged from the sizeable nearly maximum number of sign-ups even before the end of the early bird window, to the limited number of hotel rooms close to the conference venue and the lack of direct flights to Okinawa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another topic of discussion centred on how the Japanese patent attorney profession is centred in Tokyo, and only a small proportion of patent attorneys are found outside of Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact that a substantial number of Japanese firms were one or two man firms was also discussed, and the issue of leadership succession was correspondingly discussed at length.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dinner-reception-6pm--8-pm&quot;&gt;Dinner Reception (6pm – 8 pm)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was approximately an hour of speeches by executive members of the JPAA to the other members in attendance, followed by a standing-only buffet spread of exquisite Japanese cuisine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/jpaa-patent-attorneys-day-presidents-meeting-2015-dinner.jpg&quot; title=&quot;jpaa-patent-attorneys-day-presidents-meeting-2015-dinner&quot; alt=&quot;jpaa-patent-attorneys-day-presidents-meeting-2015-dinner&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/08/14/jpaa-annual-patent-attorneys-day-and-presidents-meeting/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/08/14/jpaa-annual-patent-attorneys-day-and-presidents-meeting/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the New ASPA Website</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to introduce our newly redesigned website, which has a new look and is easier to navigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website was built by committee member &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cantab-ip.com&quot;&gt;Dr Chong-Yee Khoo&lt;/a&gt;, using &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://octopress.org&quot;&gt;Octopress&lt;/a&gt;. It uses the &lt;a href=&quot;http://getbootstrap.com&quot;&gt;Bootstrap&lt;/a&gt; framework.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/08/03/new-aspa-website/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/08/03/new-aspa-website/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5th Global Forum on Intellectual Property 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA is pleased to be a supporting organisation of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipos.gov.sg/ipweek2015/&quot;&gt;5th Global Forum on Intellectual Property 2015&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipos.gov.sg/ipweek2015/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/gfip-2015.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;GFIP&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GFIP brings together internationally renowned IP legal practitioners, policy makers, members of the judiciary, academics and business leaders to share insights and strategies through a series of highly focused discussions on the latest trends and issues in the highly-evolving global IP and economic landscapes. The sterling ensemble of speakers and thought-provoking plenaries and workshops at each conference has made GFIP a must-attend event for IP leaders in the region, giving participants an opportunity to meet the Who’s Who in IP from the region and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Minister for Law will be the Guest of Honour and deliver the opening address. Other IP luminaries and policy-makers who will be speaking at GFIP 2015 include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dr. Francis Gurry, Director-General, WIPO&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Justice Colin Birss from the UK&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Simon Thorley, QC and International Judge from the Singapore International Commercialisation Court&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Judicial Commissioner George Wei&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key highlights of GFIP 2015 are-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ASEAN Economic Integration: Interoperability and Synergies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Special Judges’ Plenary Session with eminent Judges from the UK, US, China, India and Singapore&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insights into recent high-profile IP litigation cases from around the world&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discussions on IP &amp;amp; New/Disruptive Technologies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strategies for IP value creation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GFIP 2015 is also the anchor event of IP Week @ SG 2015, organized by IPOS. IP Week @ SG 2015 will be a celebration of Singapore’s achievements and milestones in IP and will showcase IP that has impacted our lives. With public talks, exhibitions and IP meeting points, this event will provide even more networking opportunities to participants and sponsors of GFIP 2015. Please refer to the following URL for more information on GFIP 2015 and IP Week @ SG 2015&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 21:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/07/07/global-forum-on-intellectual-property/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/07/07/global-forum-on-intellectual-property/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
