<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
      <title>The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA)</title>
      <description>The Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys (ASPA) is the only organisation dedicated solely to the representation of the patent profession in Singapore. Our members are patent attorneys and patent agents registered with IPOS as well as those undergoing training to qualify as patent attorneys.
      </description>
      <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.aspa.org.sg/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 09:44:02 +0800</pubDate>
      <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 09:44:02 +0800</lastBuildDate>
      <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
      <item>
        <title>ASPA End of Year Lunch 2018</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA’s annual end-of-year festive lunch will be held this year on Monday, 10 December 2018.&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Date: 10 December 2018&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Time: 12 noon to 2 pm&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Venue: Oasia Hotel Downtown, 100 Peck Seah Street, Singapore 079333&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d3988.8290970271332!2d103.84208235033091!3d1.2759016990648355!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x31da196b556291df%3A0xbc35f64ca2eb9d54!2sOasia+Hotel+Downtown!5e0!3m2!1sen!2ssg!4v1524381272716&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;An email invite will sent shortly to all members. If you wish to attend, please RSVP as soon as possible, as spaces are limited.&lt;/p&gt;
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:11:39 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2018/10/06/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2018/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2018/10/06/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2018/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASPA Annual General Meeting 2018</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An Annual General Meeting of the Association of Singapore Patent Attorneys will be held on 28 June 2018 at 6:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Date: 28 June 2018&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Time: 6 pm&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Venue: Oasia Downtown, 100 Peck Seah Street, Singapore 079333&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d3988.8290970271332!2d103.84208235033091!3d1.2759016990648355!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x31da196b556291df%3A0xbc35f64ca2eb9d54!2sOasia+Hotel+Downtown!5e0!3m2!1sen!2ssg!4v1524381272716&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The AGM will be followed by a presentation by the Executive Director of IP Valuelab (IPVL), Mr Tan Shau En. A buffet dinner will follow.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Formal notice of the AGM has been sent to members.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;It would help if you could please complete the &lt;a href=&quot;/events/agm-2018/rsvp&quot;&gt;RSVP for the 2018 AGM&lt;/a&gt; so that we may cater the right amount of food for the dinner (and have some idea of how many will turn up for the meeting).&lt;/p&gt;
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 18:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2018/05/28/aspa-annual-general-meeting-2018/</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2018/05/28/aspa-annual-general-meeting-2018/</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>ASPA End of Year Lunch 2017</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;small&gt;Updated 21 November 2017&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;This event has sold out. We look forward to seeing you at a future ASPA event.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;ASPA’s annual end-of-year festive lunch will be held this year on Friday, 1 December 2017.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Date: 1 December 2017&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Time: 12 noon to 2 pm&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Venue: Sear Steakhouse, 50 Raffles Place Level 45, Singapore Land Tower, Singapore 048623&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;del&gt;An email invite has been sent to all members. If you wish to attend, please RSVP as soon as possible, as spaces are limited.&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 00:03:11 +0800</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2017/11/22/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2017/</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2017/11/22/aspa-end-of-year-lunch-2017/</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>ASPA Response to Public Consultation on Patents</title>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Law and the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore held a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ipos.gov.sg/AboutIP/IPLegislation/PublicConsultations.aspx&quot;&gt;public consultation&lt;/a&gt; on proposed changes to the patents system in Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;After seeking members’ views, ASPA filed a &lt;a href=&quot;/files/aspa-response-to-public-consultation-on-patents-2016.pdf&quot;&gt;response to the consultation&lt;/a&gt; in November 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;!--more--&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The proposals seek to broaden the scope of Section 14(4) of the Patents Act to introduce a grace period. Under the proposed changes, a disclosure of the invention by the inventor or by a person who obtained the matter disclosed directly or indirectly from the inventor will not form part of the state of the art. This will only apply for disclosures made within 12 months before the date of filing of the patent application in Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Another signficant proposal is to amend Section 29 of the Patents Act to remove the possibility for supplementary examination, in order to “increase the quality of patents granted in Singapore”.&lt;/p&gt;
  </description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 18:41:24 +0800</pubDate>
  <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/12/17/aspa-response-to-public-consultation-on-patents/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/12/17/aspa-response-to-public-consultation-on-patents/</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>ASPA End of Year Festive Lunch</title>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;small&gt;Updated 22 November 2016&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;This event has sold out. We look forward to seeing you at a future ASPA event.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;ASPA’s annual end-of-year festive lunch will be held this year on Friday, 2 December 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Date: 2 December 2016&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Time: 12 noon to 2 pm&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Venue: Jamie’s Italian, 1 Harbourfront Walk, #1-165-167 VivoCity, Singapore 098585&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Cost: $20 members&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Please come early to catch up with your friends before 2016 ends. A three course will be served around 12:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;del&gt;An email invite has been sent to all members. If you wish to attend, please RSVP to Howard by 28 November 2016. As spaces are limited, please RSVP as soon as possible.&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 12:59:22 +0800</pubDate>
  <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/10/26/aspa-end-of-year-festive-lunch/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/10/26/aspa-end-of-year-festive-lunch/</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>ASPA Intellectual Property Seminar with CIPA</title>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce that we will be holding a half-day seminar on IP topics in early October, presented by a delegation from the UK Chartered Institute of Patent Attorneys (CIPA).&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The seminar will deal with topics of current interest in intellectual property, including:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;the impact of Brexit on European intellectual property&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;developments in European litigation procedure&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;the role of the Chartered Institute&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;conflicts of interest&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;3D trade marks&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;developments in design law&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The seminar will provide excellent networking opportunities over tea-breaks and lunch. It is open to all ordinary and associate members of ASPA as well as non-members. Advocates and solicitors who have an interest in IP law are welcome to attend.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Details of the seminar are as follow:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Date: 5 October 2016&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Time: 12 noon to 5 pm&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Venue: Pacific 1 Ballroom, Pan Pacific Hotel&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Cost: $30 members, $120 non-members (including lunch and tea breaks)&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;CPD: SILE CPD Points Pending&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;For full details of the event, please see the &lt;a href=&quot;/events/cipa-seminar-2016&quot;&gt;ASPA CIPA IP Seminar page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 14:43:54 +0800</pubDate>
  <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/09/01/intellectual-property-seminar-with-cipa/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/09/01/intellectual-property-seminar-with-cipa/</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Japan Patent Attorneys Association Visit and Seminar</title>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA was honoured to receive a delegation from the Japan Patent Attorneys Association (APAA) during a visit to Singapore in January 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/news/2016/04/20/japan-patent-attorneys-association-visit-and-seminar/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/jpaa-visit-seminar-2016.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;JPAA Visit and Seminar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;!--more--&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The visit to ASPA started with a meeting between the JPAA delegation and the ASPA Executive Committee. We discussed topics of interest to both sides and ASPA Exco members provided updates on Singapore IP law and practice.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Following the meeting, the JPAA kindly gave a presentation on “&lt;a href=&quot;/files/outline-of-patent-infringement-litigation-in-japan.pdf&quot;&gt;Patent Infringement Litigation in Japan&lt;/a&gt;” to ASPA members. The presentation was delivered by Mr Naoki Okumura of the JPAA International Activities Center.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;ASPA appreciates the opportunity to exchange views with the JPAA and we believe that such exchanges are mutually beneficial. ASPA members also appreciated the insights provided during the presentation on patent infringement in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We look forward to further cooperation with JPAA in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 11:01:08 +0800</pubDate>
  <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/04/20/japan-patent-attorneys-association-visit-and-seminar/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/04/20/japan-patent-attorneys-association-visit-and-seminar/</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>ASPA Comments on Draft Examination Guidelines for Patent Applications at IPOS</title>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;ASPA was invited by the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore to review and make comments on a proposed draft revision of the Examination Guidelines for Patent Applications at IPOS.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;!--more--&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ipos.gov.sg/Portals/0/1%20%20Examination%20Guidelines%20for%20Patent%20Applications%20at%20IPOS_ver%20Apr%202015.pdf&quot;&gt;current version of the examination guidelines&lt;/a&gt; was published by IPOS in April 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The proposed revisions are to Chapter 8 of the Guidelines and seek to clarify IPOS’s position on  examination practices regarding patentable subject matter.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In response to this invitation, ASPA submitted its &lt;a href=&quot;/files/aspa-comments-on-patent-examination-guidelines-january-2016.pdf&quot;&gt;comments on the proposed revisions to the examination guidelines&lt;/a&gt; in January 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The submissions refer to an earlier &lt;a href=&quot;/files/email-from-aspa-to-ipos-8-may-2015.txt&quot;&gt;email dated 8 May 2015 from ASPA to IPOS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 15:42:21 +0800</pubDate>
  <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/02/02/aspa-comments-on-draft-examination-guidelines-for-patent-applications-at-ipos/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/02/02/aspa-comments-on-draft-examination-guidelines-for-patent-applications-at-ipos/</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>ASPA Engages With UK Patent Attorneys</title>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;The Asian Patent Attorneys Association (APAA) 17th General Assembly 64th and 65th Council Meetings were held recently in Okinawa, Japan. Several members of ASPA’s Executive Committee attended this meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;During the meeting, we took the opportunity to make contact with members of the International Liaison Committee of the UK Chartered Institute of Patent Attorneys.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;!--more--&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;CIPA’s International Liaison Committee is responsible for co-operation with sister institutes in countries outside Europe, including the organisation of meetings between delegates of CIPA with representatives of overseas bodies both in the UK and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We are pleased to make contact with CIPA and are actively exploring the possibility of joint events between CIPA and ASPA.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://news.cipa.org.uk/20CI-3XB55-58E6171L5B/cr.aspx&quot;&gt;CIPA’s Christmas Newsletter 2015&lt;/a&gt; features a writeup on the meeting with ASPA:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“Members of CIPA’s International Liaison Committee have also met with senior members of patent and trade mark attorney institutes from Australia, New Zealand, Taiwan, Singapore and Indonesia.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;A delegation from CIPA’s International Liaison Committee, led by Chairman Richard Mair, visited Japan as observers at the Asian Patent Attorneys Association’s General Assembly. While at the event, in Okinawa, Richard and the group met attorneys from sister institutes from around the Pacific Rim to reinforce the benefits of working with the UK profession…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“While at APAA we took the opportunity to meet with sister institutes that we would otherwise find difficulty in visiting due to budgets and distances involved,” said Richard.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“The meetings with our Australian and Taiwanese colleagues have become annual fixtures. This year we also held preliminary meetings with institutes in Singapore, New Zealand and Indonesia. So I was pleased to continue strengthening existing relations and to be able to develop new ones.”&lt;/p&gt;
  </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 11:23:55 +0800</pubDate>
  <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/01/15/aspa-engages-with-uk-patent-attorneys/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2016/01/15/aspa-engages-with-uk-patent-attorneys/</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Visit of Delegation From Japan Patent Attorneys Association</title>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce that a delegation from the Japan Patent Attorneys Association (JPAA) will be visiting us on 20 January 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;!--more--&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As part of the visit, JPAA has kindly offered to give a talk “Outline of Patent Infringement Litigation in Japan” to ASPA members. All members are invited to attend this talk.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The talk will be held from 5 pm on 6.30 pm on 20 January 2016 at the Level 37 Conference Room of Spruson &amp;amp; Ferguson (Asia), at 152 Beach Road, Gateway East, Singapore 189721.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you are interested in attending the event, please get in touch with the Secretary by 31 December 2015 to register. We look forward to seeing you at the event.&lt;/p&gt;
  </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 13:11:40 +0800</pubDate>
  <link>http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/12/22/visit-of-delegation-from-japan-patent-attorneys-association/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.aspa.org.sg/news/2015/12/22/visit-of-delegation-from-japan-patent-attorneys-association/</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>